Frank Stick Papers and Artwork PC.5089
Frank Stick Papers and Artwork
- Artwork, circa 1910s-1966; 45506; Stick, Frank
  - Other Paintings and Illustrations, circa 1910s-1966; 7955; 33GRF-2; 5000.4.571; PC.5089; Painting; Stick, Frank
    - Misty Morning, PC.5089.2.183; Stick, Frank (Item Misty Morning)
    - Sunshine on the Florida Keys, PC.5089.2.184; Stick, Frank (Item Sunshine on the Florida Keys)
    - Palms, PC.5089.2.185; Stick, Frank (Item Palms)
    - Pintails, PC.5089.2.186; Stick, Frank (Item Pintails)
    - On Point, PC.5089.2.187; Stick, Frank (Item On Point)
    - Grouse, PC.5089.2.188; Stick, Frank (Item Grouse)
    - Indian on a Bucking Horse, PC.5089.2.189; Stick, Frank (Item Indian on a Bucking Horse)
    - Peacocks, PC.5089.2.190; Stick, Frank (Item Peacocks)
    - Roped, PC.5089.2.191; Stick, Frank (Item Roped)
    - Unfinished Artwork, 31965; Stick, Frank (Item Unfinished Artwork)